Baby?
Oh, you scared me.
Sorry.
Didn't mean to.
You were outside?
- Why didn't you wake me?
- I wanted to be alone.
I mean, I needed to clear my head
and get the ideas flowing.
And did they?
No.
They will.
Don't worry.
It'll come.
- I must stink.
- I like it.
I better shower.
Hey.
- Can I grab these?
- I got it.
Ooh.
Perfect.
You didn't need to do all of this.
I wanted to.
You've been working so hard.
Yeah. Right.
Wait here.
No, no, no. It's fine. It's fine.
- Come in. Please.
- Thanks. Thanks.
Oh. Hello.
Hello.
So this gentleman here
just started working
at the hospital,
and he thought we were...
- What do you do there?
- I'm an orthopedic surgeon.
Really?
But mostly now I do
research and teach.
Research.
Yes. I know, it's a bit boring.
It's not boring at all.
Sit for a second.
Can we get you anything to drink?
No. That isn't... That's fine.
- Some tea?
- Hmm?
- No, no, no, no, no.
Uh, I don't...
Uh...
I don't want to be a bother.
But you must.
A guest and a doctor?
I mean, who knows?
I might trip down the stairs one day.
Let's hope not!
- I'll go make some.
- Thank you.
This way please.
Sorry for the mess.
We're moving in
after months of construction.
It's an incredible place.
My wife loves having company.
- Your wife?
- Yes.
I thought it was your daughter.
- Sit down.
- Thank you very much.
You all right?
Fine.
Then there's this one case,
This was an opera singer,
late 20s.
Her femurs were
rotated so far inward
that she couldn't spread her knees
more than a foot apart.
Ooh, really?
- Thank you.
- You've upgraded.
- Where'd that come from?
- I always carry a supply.
I never tasted something like this.
It's hard to come by.
I had to share.
Won't you join?
Mmm. She's not much of a drinker.
I drink.
Here, let me
put a little in your tea.
I'm fine with tea, thank you.
The good doctor here
is about to publish a major paper.
"About" is generous.
I still have reams
of research to write up.
And he's moved here to finish it.
And... And what brings you to us?
Well, they told me
I could find a room here.
He thought we were
a bed and breakfast.
We always talk about
how this place
is too big for the two of us.
Well, I really should be going
if I'm going to find another...
Nonsense. No, no.
No, it's late. Stay the night.
No, I couldn't, no.
Please. We'd enjoy
the company, right?
Yes, of course.
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
Well, then I'll just grab
the rest of my stuff.
That's incredibly kind and generous.
I just left it on the...
- You all right?
- I'm fine.
You sure?
Yeah. It just went
down the wrong tube.
Thanks.
We don't know him.
He's a doctor.
He's a stranger.
We're just gonna
let him sleep in our house?
You want me to ask him to leave?
- Is that all?
- That's everything.
Um, we don't smoke.
That's smart.
In the house, I mean.
Sorry.
I'll go get you some linens.
- I'll show you to your room.
- Thank you.
Once again,
sorry for the mess.
No, please.
I really appreciate this.
Oh, and this! I love this.
How come you have so many copies?
Well, I wrote it.
Oh, my.
- That's you?
- Mmm-hmm.
- I'm a huge fan.
- You've read it?
I've read it
many, many times.
Your words have changed my life.
Oh, I'm sorry. You must...
You must hear that all the time.
Not really, no.
And that.
What is that?
Careful.
This is very, very delicate.
It was a gift.
A very special gift.
Is it from you?
No.
When I was younger,
I lost everything in a fire.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's hard to imagine
what that means.
Losing everything.
Your memories, your work,
even your dirty toothbrush.
I didn't know
if I could ever create again
until I found this in the ashes.
Isn't that remarkable?
Can I just...
It gave me the strength
to start again.
And then I met her.
You.
And she breathed life
back into every room.
She redid all of it.
Every last detail.
- By yourself?
- Mmm-hmm.
Wow.
So you're not just a pretty face.
I just came up to say
I'm gonna get ready for bed.
I'm sorry. I didn't...
You okay? Want some water?
Are you all right?
I'll be up soon.
Sure you don't want some water?
Just a little bit.
Here you go.
Sit down.
You just drank too much.
You're okay. It's okay.
Is everything all right?
He drank too much.
He'll be fine.
- What is...
- Give him some privacy.
Okay, get it up.
Just get it all up.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Smells great.
What happened last night?
I couldn't sleep. I got so excited.
From what?
His stories.
I love the man's mind.
It is so inspiring, speaking to someone
who really appreciates the work.
I love your work.
Of course you do. I know that.
So is he better?
Pardon?
Is he feeling better?
- Is he all right?
- Fine, fine. One sec.
Oh, sorry.
Just need a light.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take it outside.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
How are you feeling?
Wonderful.
You're all better?
Better?
- Morning!
- How did you sleep?
- Like a baby.
Really vivid dreams. Must be the air.
Well, I'm confused.
- Who's that?
- I'll get it.
No, don't. I'll get it.
Expecting guests?
We don't really get visitors.
That would drive me crazy.
Tell me about it.
- Hello.
- Can I help you?
- Ah, you made it!
My better half.
- Get rid of that thing, won't you?
- I'm not inhaling.
Nice to meet you.
- Oh, the pleasure is mine.
- Well, come in.
I didn't realize you were married.
Really?
Breakfast!
- I'll grab her suitcase.
- Oh.
Oh, it's burning.
- No, don't!
- Oh!
- Oh, sorry.
- I got it!
- Sit down.
- I'll get the windows.
Let me look at it.
- Are you all right?
- I think so.
You're okay. Ice.
Ice!
So stupid.
It's not bad.
It's fine. You're fine.
Oh.
- Thank you.
- I'm really so sorry.
Oh, don't worry about it.
It's very nice to meet you.
Very nice to meet... You.
Oh, please!
I'd given up on romance.
I was getting used to being alone.
Oh, thank you.
- But then...
- Yummy.
...it just happened for us.
I saw her, and I knew
she was the woman
I wanted to spend
the rest of my life with.
- Hmm. Love at first sight.
- Same here.
Yeah, right.
What? How could
I resist this face?
You believe me, right?
Come. Sit already.
- So you never had a doubt?
- That's true.
- Oh, yeah. Come on.
- What?
- Didn't you have any doubts?
- No! Not a one.
You guys understand that kind
of connection, right?
You must.
I mean, you're both so different.
It must have been
what pulled you together.
You're so beautiful. Come here.
And then the kids came
and screwed it all up.
- You have kids?
- Two.
- Boys.
- Beautiful.
Here. This is my eldest.
Let me see.
- And then her baby.
- Oh, shut up.
- Oh, amazing eyes.
- Mmm.
And you two?
You have kids?
Not yet. But we want them.
Well,
what are you waiting for?
Why not finish breakfast
and get to it?
Well, I want to finish the house,
and he's working on a new piece.
Oh, so you're writing again?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- That's wonderful.
- Finally, right?
Yes.
Oh, no. We're in the way.
That's the last thing
in the world...
No, no, not at all. No, no.
You're more than welcome
to stay here as long as you want.
That's very kind of you.
No, we couldn't impose.
Honey, they've got plenty of room.
Speaking of kids,
do you have a phone?
I can't get a signal.
That's how we like it.
You don't have
to call him every day.
There's one in the kitchen.
I can show you.
No, it's all right.
Can we just relax
for the weekend?
No, honey, I just want
to let him know we're okay.
Just a quick call.
What's wrong?
Why would you do that
without asking me?
- Do what?
- Invite them to stay.
I didn't think
it was a big deal.
- It's strange.
- What?
Did you know he had a wife?
What about your writing?
I was actually enjoying
not thinking about it.
But now that I am thinking about it,
I should go
and do something about it.
Hey. Hey.
I really should work.
Lemonade!
Oops. Oh!
Careful.
Thought you might like some.
Yes, thank you.
Secret family recipe.
Which part? The lemons?
- How's your hand?
- Mmm.
- Still stinging.
- I'm sorry.
It's not like it was your fault.
You don't have any painkillers, do you?
Are you telling me the truth?
I really don't have any.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
You're not thirsty?
Right.
Now I get it.
- It's strong.
- I'm on my second.
I can't believe you did
all this work yourself.
- Why not?
- It's a lot.
Well, we spend all our time here.
I want to make it paradise.
And I love the work.
And it's exquisite.
Thank you.
Would you take me on a tour?
Sure.
I want to thank you
for your hospitality.
Your husband has been so generous.
You're welcome.
Well, where to begin?
Well, this was the hardest part.
There was so much damage.
The treads were gone,
the railing, even the skylight.
So I had to get a lot of new material,
but I tried to save as much...
Isn't it a lot harder
than just starting fresh?
How do you mean?
Why didn't you just
build a new house?
Well, it's...
It's his home.
Oh...
You really love him.
Can I ask you a question?
Why don't you want kids?
Excuse me?
I saw how you reacted earlier.
I know what it's like
when you're just starting out,
and you think you have
all the time in the world.
You know, you're not going
to be so young forever.
Have kids.
Then you'll be creating
something together.
That's what keeps a marriage going.
This... This is all just
setting.
Oh, you do want them.
Is it him?
- I'm gonna get back to work.
- Then why did he say...
I'm sorry.
Was I too forward?
I do that sometimes.
Every relationship has its issues.
And when there's
a full generation between you,
I can only imagine.
Is that where he works?
That's private.
Oh, can't you just give me a peek?
He doesn't like anyone
being in there without him!
Wow. You really do love him.
God help you.
Where are you going?
- I'm gonna take him outside.
- We're going on a hike.
A hike?
- Me on a hike!
- Just a quick one.
Go slow.
Yeah, slow enough so my smoke
doesn't burn too quickly.
- You don't want to come?
- No, we have laundry to do.
You'll show me where, right?
- Which way?
- Doesn't matter.
- The boys have bonded, don't you think?
- Mmm-hmm.
Mine's not usually such a nature boy.
Wow. Guess you haven't quite
got to this part yet.
This is so heavy.
That's a lot of tools.
I'll get it.
- Which is which?
- On the left.
Oh, it's full.
Oh, wait! I'll help you.
Oh, no.
So that's the problem.
What?
You're gonna
have to try harder than this.
I'm sorry.
Believe me,
when they get older,
you got to keep it interesting.
He's not that old.
How's it going in that department?
I don't feel comfortable
talking about that stuff.
I'm just trying to help.
I mean, look at you.
If he's not all over you,
it's either because
of his age or...
Or what?
You know what? Forget it.
It's none of my business.
I think this has gone to my head.
No, it's okay.
Say what you were gonna say.
No, seriously. No, obviously
he still loves you.
I'm gonna freshen these up.
Hello?
Hey!
I told you, he doesn't like
anyone being in here without him.
It's amazing. What is it?
We really have to leave.
- Please?
- I just want to look at it.
You have to go.
I don't know why you have
to make such a big deal of it.
Oh, they're back.
- This way. Here.
- Honey?
- Let's get you some water.
- Are you all right
Your damn smoking.
Here.
- You all right?
- Just started.
Come on.
Let's go get you your pills.
If I wanted a third child...
I guess you overdid it.
Whew! That was intense.
And you won't believe
what he just told me.
That sink's not braced yet.
What?
Hey, wait.
Something happened?
What?
What is it? What?
He has one of those pictures of you
in his luggage.
What were you doing in their luggage?
That's not the point.
He didn't just stumble on us.
- He's a crazy fan.
- I know.
Excuse me?
That's what he told me on our walk.
He's dying.
Oh.
That's why he came here.
He wanted to meet me
before he's gone.
Well, why didn't he tell us that?
- Why lie?
- I don't know. I don't know.
He's a proud man.
I admire that.
Oh!
- What have you done?
- I'm so sorry.
We're both sorry.
I was telling her this story and...
It just... It just
fell out of my hand.
- We'll search and find you another one.
- We can pay for it.
Quiet!
I'm sorry I screamed.
I just need a moment.
It was an accident.
I think it's best if you leave.
We said we were sorry.
- Honey, don't antagonize her.
- Well, what more do you want?
Just... It'll be okay.
Please.
Please!
What are you doing?
They will never get in here again.
Well, don't worry.
I'm kicking them out.
Yeah. And where will they go?
Need something?
- Are you ready?
- What do you mean?
We want you out.
We? Or you?
- I've tried very hard...
- Yeah, well, look,
I have to check on my husband.
Hello? Hello!
Where is everybody?
Oh, hey.
Hey, who are you?
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
What are any of us doing here, right?
Where's my mother?
Uh, she's... Wait here.
Hey, nice view.
- Did you invite your son?
- What are you doing here?
Mom, I tried calling,
but I couldn't get through.
What's wrong?
He came to the house
and found the will.
- What?
- Yeah, he's out of control.
I'm sorry, but whatever this is,
- you'll have to finish this...
- Dad!
- He's here?
- What? Oh, no.
- Who's that?
- Dad! Dad!
Yeah, ran straight to Mommy.
You followed me.
What's wrong with you?
- You shouldn't be here.
- Where's Dad? Where is he?
Who is she? Who are you?
Who are you?
- He doesn't want to see you.
- That's not true. Is he here?
- Dad!
- Boys?
Boys, why are you here?
What is this? Do you know
what you've signed?
- Of course I do!
- Go lie back down.
You said that you told him.
No, honey, I didn't say that.
I was going to.
You wanted this? How could you?
It's for a good reason, son.
Let me explain to him.
- I'll talk to him.
- No, I'll talk to him.
You're right. I should
have told you myself.
And I'm sorry. I promise you
that I was thinking about you.
Stop it! About what's best
for all of us.
Just listen to Dad!
It's a trust.
You have to make a decision
as a group before
anything can be spent.
It won't work.
I have to get permission
from them every time I take a piss?
It will force you to get along.
That's the most important thing.
She will side with him every time.
You're not even listening to me!
No, no! I just want
to support both of you.
Support me?
You just want to tell me
what I can and can't do.
That is not fair!
You never believe
in me or anything I try to do.
Don't do this, Dad. They hate me!
- They don't hate you.
- We love you.
You're my son.
Well,
then treat me like one!
The sons are here.
They just barged in.
I couldn't stop them.
I know.
Yeah,
if you don't waste it all.
- Shut up!
- Here we go again.
Losing his temper
when he doesn't get his way.
Let's discuss this outside.
Our hosts are here.
No! I want to talk about it now.
- I want to talk about it now, Dad.
- Shut up!
If you need money,
I'll give you money.
I don't want your chump change!
Don't touch me!
Calm down. Calm down.
You're the poet? The great writer?
You don't know anything.
They lied to me, they're robbing me.
I don't know their story,
but will you calm down?
Will you?
Thank you.
You can sit in there.
Let's go sit down and discuss this.
No! Mom, Dad's dying,
and all he cares about
is his damn money!
- No! Stop it!
- Boys! Boys, stop it!
Look at Dad!
Look what you did!
Stop!
Boys! Stop it!
Stop! Please!
Can you breathe? Breathe.
No!
- Come here!
- Wait! Stop!
- What's wrong with you?
- Stop it!
No! Stop!
No!
No! No!
Get off!
Get up.
Get up! Get up!
Stop faking. Get up.
Get up. Look at me!
No, look. It's not my fault.
It's not my fault.
They never really loved me.
They always loved him more.
They were leaving me behind.
Just tell me you understand.
Tell me you understand!
You have to understand.
What have you done
to your brother?
My baby. My baby.
What did you do?
You did this.
Wake up! Do something! Help him!
- Towels. Towels.
- Okay.
- Easy now.
- Father...
- The doctor. Go get him.
- Okay.
- Come quick!
- What?
- What's happening?
- He's bleeding.
- It's bad! It's really bad.
- He's not waking up. He's not waking up.
Careful.
Careful! Don't drop him.
I'll call you from the hospital.
- Keep his head up.
- No! No, please stay with me.
Please, we need him.
Lock the doors.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Please don't leave me!
Hey.
They left you all alone?
You do understand.
Good luck.
911.
What's your emergency?
You all right?
He was here!
I know. I know.
The police brought me home.
They'll find him. Don't worry.
- Did he hurt you?
- No.
- No?
Okay.
Okay, sit.
Let me get you some water.
Here.
It's okay.
It's all right.
What happened at the hospital?
I was holding the boy's hand
when he died.
Oh, that's awful.
Are you all right?
I'm exhausted.
I need a hot shower.
Will you come?
Yeah.
What is it?
- I'll be up in a minute.
- You sure?
Yeah.
In here?
Yeah, straight ahead
in the kitchen.
They came back quick.
What are they doing here?
They had nowhere to go,
so I told them it would be all right
to invite some friends and family.
I'll go deal with them.
- I'm so sorry.
- Thank you.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
You're all so welcome here.
Please make yourselves at home.
I'm so sorry.
Shall we have a toast?
Yes, let's.
Make sure
everyone has one.
Would you say something?
He so respects you.
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Everyone.
Well, how can one begin
to understand your pain?
The sacrifice of the parent.
Here you go.
All those years of worry.
Years in days, days in hours,
hours in seconds.
But in each second,
an infinite amount of love.
And now,
suddenly,
it seems there is nothing to love.
Just a vast and silent darkness.
But fear not.
From inside it, there's a voice
crying out to be heard...
...loud and strong.
Just listen.
Oh, God.
Do you hear that?
That is the sound of life.
That is the sound of humanity.
That is your son's voice.
His cry of love.
His love for you.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
Hear, hear!
Thank you all for coming here
and being with us tonight.
My husband and I are so touched.
We lost our baby today.
I just...
I can't believe
that just a few hours ago,
he was standing there,
and I was holding him in my arms.
He was so full of life.
He always was.
- Hello.
- Thank you.
- Where should I put this?
- Maybe in here.
Now he'll never wander again.
I'll never hold him again
like I did today.
He'll never laugh again.
I just want to thank you all
for being here.
It means so much.
I don't know what else to say.
I just want to thank
our dear host for his hospitality
- in our time of need.
- Of course.
So, please,
I'd like to drink
to your kindness.
Excuse me.
Sweetheart,
you don't have to do this.
No, I want to.
I loved my son.
I loved him.
I can't believe this.
But I shouldn't be eulogizing him.
He'd say...
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry. I can't.
Would someone please...
Would you say something?
I...
For your child.
For both your children. Come.
Let's not forget the one
still in the wilderness.
Wherever he goes,
wherever he is...
Welcome. Please join us.
I'm just gonna put this
in the kitchen.
Yes, through there.
May he find kindness, compassion...
- I'll wait here.
- I'll be right back.
Hey, how you doing?
I'm good, considering.
Um, excuse me.
Could you get down from there?
That sink's not braced yet.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, there's glass there.
That was so beautiful, no?
It's all right.
Can I use your phone?
Sure. It's in the kitchen.
No, it's just...
Excuse me?
Where did you go?
I was just in the...
I'm really sorry, again.
I know you are.
- I can't imagine...
- No.
You can't imagine what it feels like
if you don't have a child.
You give, and you give,
and you give, and...
It's just never enough.
- I understand.
- Do you?
Why don't you at least
put on something decent?
Hey!
You can't be in here.
- I'm sorry?
- You need to leave.
- We'll just be a minute.
- This is our room!
It's okay.
It's your room.
Come on.
Let's find another spot.
Oh.
Excuse me.
Just exploring.
Could you please go downstairs?
- This way?
- Yes.
Sure.
What is...
What are you doing?
Oh, it's no big deal.
I worked my way
through college doing this.
But why are you painting my house?
Well, he's been so kind to everyone,
it's the least we could do.
Stop!
Both of you. Stop!
No problem.
Yes, of course.
What's mine is yours.
There you are!
My goddess. Come here.
Please, make some room for her.
You've got to hear these stories.
All these people!
I know. They're just letting off steam.
They're painting our house!
Oh!
You all right?
I told you to stop drinking.
I got it.
- Napkins!
- Yeah, I got some.
Are you all right?
The chair might not be all right.
After spending
a few days with my mother...
Please! Get down from there.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
- What's her problem?
- I don't know.
Hey, we haven't met.
I've known this family for years.
And you?
This is my house.
Well, it's a beautiful home.
You want to take a walk?
- What?
- A walk. With me.
No. No.
Please!
- Take my number.
- No, I don't want your number.
Why would you say that?
You don't even know me.
- Let go of me!
- Why?
Because I don't know you.
- Get down from there.
- From where?
You don't know
what I could do for you.
I don't want anything from you.
Sassy.
Leave me alone.
You know what?
Get out of my face.
You're an arrogant cunt.
This sink.
There's nothing wrong with it.
It's really okay.
No, stop doing that.
Don't do that. Stop!
Stop doing that! Stop, stop!
Get out! Get out, all of you!
What happened?
They won't listen!
It's all right. We'll fix it.
It can be fixed.
- We're being punished.
- Please, don't go. Don't go.
- We'll turn it off.
- It's been an honor.
We will never forget
all you've done for us.
But where will you go?
They're gone.
Come. Let's go to bed.
You don't need to do that.
Do what?
Clean up their mess?
We did a good thing.
They needed a place
to celebrate life.
They needed tonight.
What about what I needed?
A boy died here today.
I mopped up his blood.
- And you abandoned me.
- No, no, I didn't abandon you.
They just lost a son.
They lost, well, two sons!
I was helping them.
This is not about us. It's about them.
No! It's not about them.
It's about you.
It's always about you
and your work.
You think that's gonna help you write?
Nothing does!
I rebuilt this entire house,
wall to wall.
You haven't written a word!
I know! I know! I'm sorry!
I can't... I can't write!
I can't think!
All I'm trying to do
is bring life into this house!
Open the door
to new people, new ideas.
You think you can't breathe?
I'm the one who's suffocating here
while you pretend
that nothing is wrong!
"Everything will be all right.
Everything will be good.
"You'll be fine."
You know what?
Life doesn't always work out
the way you want it to.
You're right.
Mine certainly didn't.
Excuse me?
You talk about wanting kids,
but you can't even fuck me.
- Come here. Come here!
- No! No!
I'm pregnant.
Hmm?
We're gonna have a baby.
I'm serious.
How could you know?
Because I know.
I'm pregnant.
A baby...
- Are you happy?
- Happy?
That's the most beautiful gift.
What?
Pen, pen, pen.
What are you doing?
I'm writing.
- What?
- Writing.
Last night, those people.
Their pain. Their love
behind the pain. And then...
You.
Us.
And now that.
Life.
It's coming to me. It's...
I know what to say.
I have to find the words. That's all.
Amazing.
Well, I won't...
I don't want to interrupt.
I'll just get started
on the apocalypse.
Hey.
I love you.
It moved! It moved!
What is it?
Is that it?
I finished it.
May I?
It's beautiful.
Really?
Why are you crying?
It's just a lot.
You think it's good?
It's perfect.
But then what's going on?
Am I going to lose you?
Never.
Hello?
Hi.
Yes?
Really?
- Really.
- Who is that?
One moment. Give me a second.
They loved it.
Who did?
What? Yeah, I'll be here,
standing by.
Are you there? Hello?
- Who was that?
- My publisher.
- She's read it?
- Yes. Of course. Why?
Yes.
Hi, again.
Press? Uh, well, you know
how I feel about it.
I'd rather not.
But if you think it's a must.
I'll be here, waiting.
Wow, amazing!
Well, we're celebrating.
One day, every copy sold.
You're so beautiful.
Make yourself comfortable.
I'll go get everything.
Looks delicious.
- Let me help you.
- No, sit.
No, I'm helping.
Okay.
Will you bring the bread in?
All right.
No. Wait, please.
Can I see him?
Excuse me,
I have a question.
What are you doing?
- Who are they?
- I don't know.
Please. Wait.
What do they want?
I don't know.
They've come here to see me.
Please! I just want to
get a photo with him.
He'll be back in a moment.
Just keep everything warm.
I'll be right in.
You had a question.
- Yeah.
- What is it?
As I was saying, we've
all traveled a great distance,
and I feel that, uh...
Well, these words,
I feel like they were written for me.
Of course they were.
My goddess! Come here.
Come.
- No, stay away from me!
- Please leave her. Thank you.
They love it.
They understand all of it.
But it affects everyone
in a different way.
It is remarkable.
Come. They want to meet you.
No, I don't want to.
I don't want to. Come inside.
But they've come from so far.
Look at me!
I'm about to have our baby.
Why is that not enough for you?
Of course it's enough.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm here, with you.
I want to be alone with you.
I'm with you.
Give me a second.
Come, come, come.
Quick, quick.
Just hang in there. Hold it in.
Hey!
I'm sure there's a bathroom
really close.
- Hold it in.
- Excuse me.
Do you know where the bathroom is?
- You need to leave.
- Where should I go?
I don't know,
but you can't be in here.
But my son, he, um...
Oh...
Okay. Come with me.
Thank you so much.
I'll come back and clean up.
Did you open this?
Okay, here we go.
Just a little bit longer.
It's okay.
We'll get you dried off.
After you've finished,
I really need you to go back outside.
What are you doing?
How about a little privacy?
Please?
Sir!
I've been waiting
a long time. Excuse me.
- Hey, wait your turn, lady.
- No!
How did you get in here?
Could you get the two of us, please?
- No, I got it. I got it.
- Thanks.
- Okay, get down on the floor.
- It's beautiful.
Don't touch that!
It's so organic.
Hey, stop pushing!
All of you need to go outside.
Hey! Sir!
I'm just gonna lie down for a bit.
I don't feel so good.
- No, no, you cannot lie down here.
- Why? You staying in here?
I live here. This is my house.
"My house"? "My house"?
The poet says it's everyone's house!
Food and drink, my friends.
I believe it's, um,
yes, right back here.
Hey!
Oh, this is nice.
We've got vegetables...
Stop! All of you.
Check the cabinets.
And the fridge!
What are you doing?
Oh, beautiful!
No! No! That's not for you.
He said to share.
But it's not yours!
They're hungry and thirsty.
Here you go.
Now, take the fruit and
the cheese and the pickles.
Excuse me. Watch your backs.
You can put that over there.
And that goes over there. Thank you.
Looks great, let's share it.
I'll slice this up.
You can sit here, sir.
There'll be
no photos, just autographs!
Your writing is so beautiful.
What is this? What are you doing?
I'm showing them my appreciation.
- Hey!
- Oh, hi!
Oh! My genius.
Look at you.
- The second printing is here.
- Great.
Yes. I wish you would've told me
about this turnout.
- Have you met my...
- There she is.
Oh...
The inspiration.
All right, I have to be honest.
I was a little worried about him
being holed up here with you.
I was nervous
you'd never write again.
Of course not.
But whatever you did,
it was worth it.
And look at you.
You're ready to pop!
How are you feeling? Hot?
It's hot in here.
Is it me? It's broiling.
I've got it right here.
Oh, yes. Will you excuse me?
Let me see. Take it out!
Oh, yes.
That's exactly what I wanted.
- Um, the original, where is it?
- It's right there by the desk.
- I've got it!
- Excuse me.
- I've got it.
- I'll take that, thank you.
- Oh. No, it's okay.
- No, don't touch it!
- No, it's fine.
- Don't touch it!
- No! Get your hands off it!
- What happened?
Wait, wait! Easy, easy, easy.
I'm trying to put it
in this frame.
Okay, I'll do it.
It's all good.
Hey!
Stop! Give that back. Give it back.
No, I have to have
something of his! No!
It's mine!
You did it! Now I got to find
something else!
Get out! All of you!
Stop! This doesn't belong to you!
911.
What's your emergency?
Can you help me?
What is your emergency, ma'am?
They're stealing everything!
Thank you.
I was using that!
That's all right.
Share, like the poet said.
Yeah, share.
That's not right.
Look, he marked you.
He marked you.
- Me, too. Please.
- Okay.
- Oh, thank you.
- Stop!
Stop! Stop touching him!
They're ruining everything.
Those are just things.
They can be replaced. Don't worry.
- Forgive me. Just a few shots.
- Of course.
- Here we go.
- No!
Look right in the lens,
make sure you're getting him.
No, no, no, no, don't go!
Please, just one more!
You're welcome to
pin your thanks on the door.
His words are yours.
Gracias.
Watch your step going down.
Next, please. Step forward.
His words are yours.
If you please,
pin your thoughts on the wall.
Step forward.
- His words are yours.
- Thank you.
Next.
There you are!
Where have you been hiding?
Why are you doing this?
Proof we were here.
- Get off of me!
- What the hell!
I'll kill you!
- Watch your back.
- Heads up. Coming through.
No! Don't.
- Hey!
- No! Let go!
No, you can't leave! He loves you!
I got it. Where are you going?
Don't. Don't go.
You don't want me here.
Come here. Look here.
- I'm here.
- I can't.
Listen, I have to
tell you something.
What?
The baby? The baby?
- Come here. Come, come.
- Lock the back door!
We need space! We need space!
Hold on here. I'll be right back.
Back! Back! Give us some room!
Police!
Get on the ground!
Help me. Help me. No!
Against the wall!
Please don't! My baby! Please don't!
Get off her! Get off!
Back off!
I call dibs!
Ah!
Where you going, huh?
Get inside!
Somebody help us, please!
Shut up!
- How's Angel?
- Tainted.
Check the goyim.
Move!
- I didn't do anything!
- Get in there!
- Quiet!
- Keep your mouths shut.
The inspiration!
Where have you been hiding?
Finish her.
On your knees!
All right, six more.
Disperse!
Freeze!
Oh, no. Come on.
Are you hurt?
The baby...
Medic!
This way.
Go, hurry. Just go!
My darling! It's me! It's me.
What's happening?
I don't know.
I have to take you somewhere safe.
- There.
- No, no, no.
- Out!
- It's too dangerous.
Come with me. Quietly.
This way.
- The door!
- No, no, it's this way.
It's him! It's the poet!
He hasn't forsaken us after all!
We need to hurry. Stay close.
We need money!
We need to eat! Please!
Get back! Get back!
Please, no, I can't! I can't!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I can't!
I will not forget you.
Poet, over here! Come on!
Up here! Up here!
Up there! Up there.
They will protect us.
Come. I've got you.
Grab the hand.
Get back! Get back! I will return!
Hold them back!
Sit here. Rest.
- I'm a doctor!
- A doctor? Please help her.
Help her, please. Here.
I'll be right back.
Oh, that's good.
Don't leave us!
Get off!
Look at me.
Listen to my voice.
The baby's almost here.
Just a little bit further.
You can do this.
Push.
Just push.
- No.
- Yes, yes!
You have to push. Push!
Push. You're almost there. Yes!
Do it again.
Yes, you're doing very good.
- I can feel the head.
- Please move. I've got her.
- Wait! I can help.
- I'm delivering my baby!
- Let me help!
- Shut the door!
Shut it!
We're safe.
It's okay. Our baby's coming.
Our baby's coming.
Okay.
It's almost here.
It's here.
It's coming. It's coming!
It's a boy.
It's a boy, look.
Cover him.
What's happening?
Why are they so quiet?
I don't know.
Don't!
Don't do that.
It's okay.
Shut the door.
Seal it!
They brought us gifts.
- Here.
- What are they doing?
They're just waiting.
Waiting for what?
I don't know.
Make them go.
Please.
Please make them.
- Please.
- Okay, okay.
More gifts. Look. Look.
For you. Clean clothes.
Are they leaving?
What?
No, they...
They just want to see him.
No.
Make them go.
I can't. I can't.
Yes, you can! They adore you.
They would listen to you.
- Why won't you?
- I don't want them to go!
He's beautiful.
- Let me hold him.
- No.
Okay, let me hold him.
- Let me hold my baby.
- No.
- Let me hold him.
- I'm his father!
- I'm his mother!
- Here, let me...
- No!
Please?
Please make them go.
No. No. No.
No!
Give me back my baby!
Where is he?
Wait! Stop!
No! That's my baby!
No! No! Give me back...
- Hallelujah!
- Praise be!
Hallelujah!
You're gonna hurt him!
Please! Please! Please!
You're hurting him! You're hurting him!
Where is he?
- Where's my baby?
- He's not dead.
- What? Where is he?
- A voice
still cries out to be heard,
loud and strong.
- Listen.
- What?
Do you hear that?
No! No!
That's the sound of life.
The sound of humanity!
His cry of love!
His love for you!
Get off! Get off!
You killed him!
- Die, cunt!
- Dirty whore!
Slut! Bitch!
Fat pig!
You bitch!
Take that, tramp!
- Cunt!
- Kill the pig!
Please!
Please stop! Stop, please!
Go away. Leave her alone.
What are you doing?
Look what they've done to you.
They killed my baby!
You killed him.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
They just want to see him.
They just want to touch him,
and then they...
It was...
It's horrible. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
But we can't...
We can't let him die for nothing.
We can't.
Maybe what happened
could change everything.
Everyone.
- What are you talking about?
- We...
You and I, we have to find
a way to forgive them.
They butchered our son!
I know. I know.
You're insane.
- Listen to me.
- You're insane.
Well, listen to them.
They are so sorry.
They are truly sorry.
Listen. Have faith in me.
Please. Please.
We need to forgive them.
We need to forgive them!
Please. Please! We have to!
No!
Murderers!
Murderer!
It's time to get the fuck
out of my house!
No, no. No, no, no!
No! Please! Don't leave!
Please! I beg you!
Don't run off! We will rebuild!
Don't! Don't leave me alone!
This way!
She went down here!
Stop! Stop! Wait. Wait.
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Please don't.
I love you.
You never loved me.
You just loved
how much I loved you.
I gave you everything!
You gave it all away.
No. No. No.
No, no, no, no!
What are you?
Me?
I am I.
You?
You were home.
Where are you taking me?
The beginning.
Is that it?
It won't hurt much longer.
What hurts me the most
is that I wasn't enough.
It's not your fault.
Nothing is ever enough.
I couldn't create if it was.
And I have to. That's what I do.
That's what I am.
Now I must try it all again.
No.
Just let me go.
I need one last thing.
I have nothing left to give.
Your love.
It's still there, isn't it?
Go ahead.
Take it.
Baby?